atmgreetings.com 2012-06-11

# atmgreetings.com : Privacy Policy

**Privacy policy**

Overview 

atmgreetings.com (ATM) is a provider of free greeting cards on the Internet. This Overall Privacy Statement discloses the privacy practices for the entire atmgreetings.com website. 

ATM", protecting our users' privacy and security is a top priority. For this reason, we have adopted the following policy to advise you of our use of your personal information online and your choices regarding that use. This policy describes what types of information we gather about you, how we use it, under what circumstances we disclose it to third-parties, and your rights to update or correct it. 

Scope of Policy 

This Policy applies to all atmgreetings.com, including our co-branded sites as may be launched subject to changes from time to time as the circumstances may require. This Policy does not apply to other companies' or organizations' web sites to which we link. You should carefully review the privacy policies of those web sites in order to determine how they treat your personal information. 

What Information does atmgreetings.com collect? 

Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with the best and most useful content and services. Because we derive revenue mainly from advertising, collecting information is essential to keep our services affordable to users. 

We collect personal information about our users during usage of the atmgreetings.com service, from our use of 'cookie' technology as and when you use the service and during sending or viewing an ecard through atmgreetings.com or while subscribing to our newsletter and special offer services. 

Information About You Information Gathered From All Visitors Aggregate Data 

We gather certain generic information with respect to customers' use of our web site, such as the number of unique visitors, the frequency with which they visit, and the areas on the web site that they favor. These statistics are very much like television ratings that tell the networks how many people tuned in to a program. We only use this type of data in aggregate-that is, we look at the data on a collective basis, in summary form, rather than on an individual basis. This data helps us determine the extent to which our customers use certain parts of our web site, which, in turn, enables us to make it as appealing as possible. We may also provide statistical "ratings" about how our customers collectively use our web site to advertisers, sponsors, and other companies with which we do business ("Business Partners"). We do this so they, too, can understand how often people use their areas of the site in order for them to provide you with the best possible experience. These statistical ratings do not contain any personally identifiable information about you or any of our users. 

Cookies 

We use a technology nicknamed "cookies" on our web site. Cookies are pieces of information or data sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies to make your visit to our web site easier. For example, cookies allow us to recognize you when you re-enter our web site so that you will not have to sign-in each time you visit. Cookies also allow us to count the number of unique and return visitors who use our site. 

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can reset your browser to notify you when you've received a cookie or, alternatively, to refuse to accept cookies. It is important to note that you may not be able to use certain features on our web site if you choose not to accept cookies, such as Create & Print, My Page, address book, favorites, and ecard history. In addition, you will not be able to participate in any of our sweepstakes, or contests. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance their experience on our site. 

What is atmgreetings.com's practice regarding cookies? 

Your Internet browser has a feature called "cookies" which stores small amounts of data on your computer about your visits to Internet websites. You do not need to have cookies turned on to visit atmgreetings.com. Cookies alone tell us nothing about who you are unless you specifically give us personally identifiable information which we may use to enhance your services in the ways described herein. You may choose not to allow cookies to be collected by adjusting your settings on your browser. 

We use technologies, including electronic images known as Web beacons (called a transparent GIF or single-pixel GIF) that allow us to track general user traffic patterns. We also automatically receive and record information from our servers and from your browser, including your IP address, the time of your visit to pages on our website, and information about pages you visited. The information we gather through the use of tracking technologies cannot be matched with any personally identifiable information about you unless you have specifically given us personally identifiable information. We may use the information to enhance your services in the ways described below. 

  * We use cookies and tracking technologies in a variety of ways, including: 

  * Keeping count of return visits to our website or our advertisers' or partners' websites. 

  * Accumulating and reporting anonymous, aggregate (data collected in mass), statistical information on website and advertisement usage. 

  * Determining which features our overall user population likes best. 

  * Saving your name & e-mail address so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our website. 

  * Display the most appropriate advertising based on your interests. 

We allow other companies that are presenting advertisements on our websites and, sometimes, in our newsletters to use tracking technology on your computer. We do not give any personally identifiable information to them as part of this relationship. Unless you visit the website of these companies and provide them with personally identifiable information about yourself, these tracking technologies tell those advertisers nothing about who you are. Our advertisers' use of tracking technology is subject to their own privacy policies. 

Editing Your Profile 

You have the ability to review and correct your personally identifiable information at any time. Simply click on the "My Account" link at the top of the every page to the "My Profile" page. There, you can change your address information, e-mail type, sign-in, and e-mail permissions. You can revise, add, delete, or completely cancel all alerts by clicking the "Reminders" links at the top of each page. 

How does atmgreetings.com use the information it collects? 

We use the information we gather for the following purposes: 

  * To customize the advertising and content you see 
  * To enhance the user experience in our website. We use tracking information to determine how well each page performs overall based on aggregate user demographics and traffic patterns to those pages. This helps us to continue to build a better service for you. 
  * To fulfill your requests for fresh content and services. 
  * To send you information you agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to you. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies,[click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).
